healthifyme.com 2012-11-19

# HealthifyMe

This Privacy Statement informs users of the healthifyMe website about how Caeruz Ventures Private Limited, trading as healthifyMe ("healthifyMe" or "we") gathers and uses personal information submitted to healthifyMe and aggregated information collected from the healthifyMe website. 

### Collection of personal information

If you use the healthifyMe website, you may enter data into the it, by providing an email address and password, in order to set, track and manage your diet and exercise goals. This data, your "Personal Diet Data", includes your birthdate, your height and weight, your gender, and specific details of the foods and drinks that you consume and the exercise you do. 

In addition to the above personal information, we collect standard information about healthifyMe users such as IP addresses, browser type, operating system, pages visited on our site, referring and exit pages, and the dates and times of the visits. This site visitation data is used to administer the site and provide general statistics regarding the use of healthifyme.com. Site visitation data is never linked to your personal information, and we do not use it to identify you individually. 

### Use of personal information

We will treat your Personal Diet Data as confidential, and we will not share your personal information or Personal Diet Data with third parties without your permission, except in the limited circumstances described below. 

We will use the personal information you give us to fulfill the services and products you request from us. This may include billing and shipping of products that you order, sending information that you have requested, or contacting you about products and services that you have purchased. In some circumstances we may use third party contractors to perform these services on our behalf. In such circumstances, we will only provide the contractor with the information needed to perform the services (for example, name and address if a contractor is delivering a product to you), and all contractors will be required to agree to confidentiality obligations with respect to your personal, non-public information. 

If you do not opt-out of communications from healthifyMe, we may send you marketing notices including promotions of our products and services. You can opt-out of communications from healthifyMe at any time (see control of personal information below). 

We may disclose your personal information when we reasonably believe that it is required by a law or legal process and to protect and defend the rights and interests of healthifyMe, its affiliates, suppliers, or users. In the event healthifyMe goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information and Personal Diet Data will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. 

We may use and disclose Personal Diet Data, in a form that does not identify any individual, to allow healthifyMe and our advertisers to present targeted advertising to you. We may disclose to third parties, including advertisers and potential business partners, aggregated statistics that we develop from Personal Diet Data. For example, we may disclose the total number of pounds lost by all healthifyMe users, the average weight loss of healthifyMe users, or generalized information about diet and exercise habits based on aggregated statistics developed from Personal Diet Data. This statistical information will not identify any individual. 

### Control of personal information

You can confirm, change, or update personal information you have provided to us by contacting us directly at [help@healthifyme.com](mailto:help@healthifyme.com) with your request. 

If you want to opt-out of communications from healthifyMe, you can do so by emailing your request to [help@healthifyme.com](mailto:help@healthifyme.com). If you change your mind, you can opt-in again, by emailing this same address. When you opt-out of promotional communications from us, you may still receive service messages (such as an order confirmation) and legally mandated notices. 

### Security of the information we collect

We use a range of technologies and procedures to protect your personal information. For example, we store personal information and Personal Diet Information in a secure, limited access facility, and we use industry-standard firewalls and security software design to protect the security and integrity of your Personal Diet Information. 

### Protection of children's privacy

healthifyme.com is a general interest website, and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children. If you are under 18, you are not permitted to use healthifyme.com. 

### Use of cookies and tracking technology

When you visit our site, a cookie may be saved on your computer (if your computer accepts cookies), and if you return to the site the cookie may be read. We use cookies to help us collect the site visitation data described above and in some cases to deliver specialized content. Cookies are not linked to your personal information. 

We may also use web beacons, clear gif technology, or action tags as mechanisms to collect aggregate site visitation data by tracking how users navigate to and through our website. We may also use this technology to track the delivery of HTML email messages. Data collected through this mechanism is not linked to personal information. 

Some of the analytics technology described in this section is provided to us by Google, Inc ("Google"). Under the Google Analytics Terms of Service, Google and its subsidiaries have the right to retain and use the anonymous traffic data collected by the Google Analytics service from users of this website or the healthifyMe iPhone application. Google's use of such data is subject to the Google Privacy Policy located at <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>. 

### Enforcement of this statement

If you have questions about the policies described in this statement, please email us directly at [help@healthifyme.com](mailto:help@healthifyme.com). 

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites, and we encourage you to review the policies of each site you use. 

### Changes to this statement

We may from time to time update this privacy statement. When we make these updates, we will change the "last updated" date listed below. If we make a major change to this statement, we will update users by placing a more prominent notice on our home page. Your use of healthifyMe after an updated privacy statement becomes effective will indicate your acceptance. 

### Users from outside the India

healthifyMe is subject to the applicable laws of the India. If you use healthifyMe, you consent to the use and disclosure of information in accordance with this privacy statement and subject to such laws. 

### Contact information

We welcome your input on our privacy statement. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy statement, please contact us at help@healthifyme.com. 

Last Updated: August 25, 2012
